export const getApplicationsSuccess = {
    "cohort_apps" : [
        {
            "id": "5bCkGrULvtPQNxwtRGeI",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development",
            "questions": [{
                "timestampForKey": 1576005586574,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "q 1",
                "isRequired": true
            }],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-24T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2019-12-31T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-11T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "yena test"
        }, {
            "id": "A9R5X5wkChNp20Gt2cOl",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Product Design",
            "questions": [{
                "isRequired": true,
                "timestampForKey": 1575414670845,
                "options": ["one", "two"],
                "type": "checkboxes",
                "prompt": "test 1"
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1575414731011,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "test1 ",
                "isRequired": false
            }],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-24T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2019-12-30T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-18T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "cohrot 202"
        }, {
            "id": "BujiJw3CEodUPBqx9luO",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development",
            "questions": [],
            "dateClose": "2020-01-07T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2020-01-10T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2020-01-04T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "testing sogol's endpoint conditional"
        }, {
            "id": "CssgRFz1kfI362jluCNW",
            "questions": [{
                "timestampForKey": 1575856416240,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "sdsd",
                "isRequired": true
            }],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-19T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2019-12-10T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-11T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "cohort 1000",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development"
        }, {
            "id": "FEsiALoVuwnRUMLfTZjx",
            "cohortName": "lala",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Backend Development",
            "questions": [{
                "timestampForKey": 1575348543996,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "something?",
                "isRequired": true
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1575348548884,
                "options": ["this", "that", "other"],
                "type": "dropdown",
                "prompt": "other than?",
                "isRequired": true
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1575348559154,
                "options": [],
                "type": "paragraph",
                "prompt": "lala?",
                "isRequired": false
            }],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-24T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2019-12-27T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-04T05:00:00.000Z"
        }, {
            "id": "JIrGwGk9FlqnG7XSaBtl",
            "dateOfResponse": "2020-01-27T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-27T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "cohort 100",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development",
            "questions": [],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-31T05:00:00.000Z"
        }, {
            "id": "JJHlq01j4Wcy0xuRPxNI",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-19T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "semantic ui form",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Product Design",
            "questions": [{
                "timestampForKey": 1576009914073,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "semantic ui question 1",
                "isRequired": true
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1576009955480,
                "options": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
                "type": "drop-down",
                "prompt": "semantic ui question 2",
                "isRequired": false
            }],
            "dateClose": "2020-01-01T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2020-01-14T05:00:00.000Z"
        }, {
            "id": "NXK1q4PhBsIWEUArKaEF",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-28T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "cohort 100",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Backend Development",
            "questions": [],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-30T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2020-01-02T05:00:00.000Z"
        }, {
            "id": "RgH3N8LRYEtP9V6PXC0Q",
            "questions": [{
                "timestampForKey": 1576022943710,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "Yena test",
                "isRequired": false
            }],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-13T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2019-12-16T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-11T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "cohort Yena test",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development"
        }, {
            "id": "e4ySYEAgE8sZaqLw1E3i",
            "dateClose": "2020-03-20T04:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOfResponse": "2020-03-27T04:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-09T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "The Test",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development",
            "questions": [{
                "timestampForKey": 1575952961493,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "Describe your day?",
                "isRequired": true
            }, {
                "isRequired": true,
                "timestampForKey": 1575952978014,
                "options": [],
                "type": "paragraph",
                "prompt": "Describe your pet?"
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1575952989226,
                "options": ["red", "blue", "green", "yellow"],
                "type": "checkboxes",
                "prompt": "Best color",
                "isRequired": true
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1575953008145,
                "options": [],
                "type": "short-answer",
                "prompt": "Question not required?",
                "isRequired": false
            }, {
                "timestampForKey": 1575953025068,
                "options": ["yes", "no", "maybe"],
                "type": "dropdown",
                "prompt": "Some kind of dropdown?",
                "isRequired": true
            }]
        }, {
            "id": "fkRhEe6lcUmI6RyEvUQP",
            "dateOfResponse": "2019-12-19T05:00:00.000Z",
            "dateOpen": "2019-12-10T05:00:00.000Z",
            "cohortName": "test 2",
            "link": "/",
            "cohortType": "Frontend Development",
            "questions": [],
            "dateClose": "2019-12-12T05:00:00.000Z"
        }
    ]
}

export const getCohortSuccess = [

]
